Whoo!
Two, three.
Oh, my!
Here we go, y'all!
Zoidberg. Zoidberg.
Z-Z-Z-Z-Zoidberg.
This is a story
about all my friends.
Why? Why?
Previously on All My Circuits...
I'm sorry, Father,
but somewhere along the way,
I forgot how to be your son.
Why, Antonio?
Because I have amnesia!
Calculon!
But I thought you were...
Egyptian?
Before I kill you,
I must ask you one question.
Who am I?
For I have amnesia!
Let me get this straight.
Does anyone here not have amnesia?
I don't know.
This show is awesome.
When I grow up, I'm going
to have so much amnesia.
Me, too.
I mean, I have it now, but I forgot.
Well, mine's louder.
Cram a ham in it, you twerps.
Sorry.
Nah, I had it coming.
Welcome, swingers.
Pull up a groove and get fabulous.
Nude rock bands,
big piles of what I assume
is talcum powder...
It's quite a birthday party, Calculon.
Cool!
I'm going to have
a fabulacious birthday party
just like Calculon.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I'm going to show up looking good
just like Monique.
Do you two have to imitate
everything you see on TV?
Um, we're 12, so yes.
Hold up, Cubert.
You're a clone of the professor.
Do clones even have birthdays?
Um, duh.
Duh, what?
Dad, do I have a birthday?
Hmm.
You didn't have a birth,
so technically, no.
Oh, don't feel bad.
We can celebrate the day
I extracted you from the cloning tank.
Or the day I scraped your DNA
from that growth on my back.
Ooh, that one!
Ah, yes, it was 13 years ago next week.
I used this very fork.
Oh, well, isn't that...
Hey, next week will be my birthday, too.
That's true.
If only there were a way to have
one party for both of you
here at the office,
then write it off as a business expense.
Wait! I thought of a way.
The way I just said.
- Yeah.
- Way to go, Pops.
Something's happening
on television!
Oh, Monique, why did we wait so many years
to bathe in champagne?
Father!
I've discovered the shocking secret
Mother has kept from you for 200 years.
No! No!
Brace yourself,
for whenI speak these words,
you may well suffer an attack
of explosive amnesia.
For you see, the horrible secret is...
Whoever's directing this
is a master of suspense.
He's busteds.
Let's get hims out of heres.
We now join
America's most popular show
already in progress...
Everybody Loves Hypnotoad.
This show's been going downhill
since Season 3.
Look who's here, everyone.
It's Zoidberg, the lovable tramp.
Since when are you performing
at children's parties?
Performing? What?
Please, if someone
could spare me money to buy shoes?
This party pukes.
Yeah, the guests were supposed to be here
three hours ago.
Well, that doesn't mean
that no one is coming
or that you two are total losers.
Who gave you that idea?
All right.
They must have all come as a group.
Welcome, swingers.
Pull up a groove and get fabulous.
Uh?
Huh?
Good day, fellows.
Someone dumped this invitation
in my begging cup.
Happy growth-scraping day to all!
Fire them all.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Guys, guys!
Something's happening on television again.
Ooh!
Welcome to Entertainment
and Earth Invasion Tonite.
Across the galaxy,
my people are completing
the mighty space fleet
that will exterminate the human race.
But first, this news from Tinseltown.
Following Antonio Calculon, Jr.'s
breakdown on the set,
the popular TV show All My Circuits
will hold an open casting call
for child robots to replace him.
An open casting call for child robots?
Tinny Tim, are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
What's that, sir?
That I, Bender, am perfect for the role.
You raised my hopes and
dashed them quite expertly, sir.
Bravo!
Bender, your swarthy Latin charm
will only get you so far.
There's a lot of famous
child acting units here.
Look! There's Macaulay Cul-Con.
He's just not cute
since he got puberty installed.
Psst! There's that robot child actor
who grew up and robbed
the convenience store.
And there's that robot child actor
who grew up and became
a convenience store.
Lottery ticket, please.
We're ready for the first audition.
Emotitron, Jr.
Hold on, precious.
Let's make you look nice for the lady.
What's this? What did I tell you?
No more hanging wires!
In this scene,
you've just found out your real father
is Calculon's fourth
evil identical septuplet, Sleazy Martinez.
Okay, take us there.
"Now that I know the truth,
Father, I must ride south
"and join the robo-bandidos
at Veracruz..."
Boo! Boo!
This kid sucks!
We want Bender!
Boo!
Well, I thought he was good
but the audience seems
to have turned on him.
- But I don't think...
- Next!
"...at Veracruz.
"So, if you'll kindly
hand me my poncho..."
Boo! Bring on Bender!
Boo! Bender's the greatest!
Sorry, kid. You're flailing up there.
Oh!
Ninety actors and they all got booed.
I just wish we could get this "Bender"
I keep hearing about.
They say he's the greatest.
Well, there is a robot named Bender here
but he's much too old...
Send him in forthwith!
Boo! Not as good as Bender!
Boo!
Mr. Bender?
Have you ever been on TV before?
Once, when I took those hostages.
I saw that. You were good.
Let's hear you audition.
Bandidos, eh?
Ah, this is great,
'cause I happen to have
a flawless Spanish accent.
"I will say a-dee-os, Pad-ray.
"Come, Jesus, my faithful chi-hew-a-hew-a.
"Tonight, we eat gyoo-a-ca-mole
"by the el rio."
That was so terrible,
I think you gave me cancer.
I don't care how popular you are,
you will never work on my show!
Yay, Bender!
We demand Bender!
However, you've got the job.
Welcome aboard, "son."
Fathero!
Bender, I'd like you to meet our director
whose name I never learned.
Yo.
I read the script and I think
it would help my character's motivation
if he was on fire.
Uh, don't worry about the script, baby.
We rewrote your part to better
suit your acting abilities.
So, now my character has a British accent?
No, now your character's in a coma.
Get in bed and don't move.
And, action!
Stupid, dumb coma.
Could have been British.
Alas, that mine only son
should sink into an
irreversible, permanent...
...coma.
Permanent? That's completely
out of character for Antonio.
I'm getting up.
Curse the tragic wildebeest
accident that...
Hey, everyone!
Antonio here, but you can call me Bender.
I got ants in my butt
and I needs to strut.
Come on, baby, do, ah, do.
Dee, dah, doda, booba
Dah, boo, come on
Do, dee, bee, bah, boo...
I'm not familiar with
the type of thing I'm seeing.
Bite my shiny metal ass.
Ooh, yeah, come on, baby, yeah
Ooh, uh, come on, yeah...
Cut!
That's the worst coma acting
I've ever seen!
We'll have to shoot it again.
No. No, no, no, I don't do two takes.
But this guy was...
Amateurs like you do two takes.
I do one take.
Print it.
I'll be in my three-story trailer.
Bite my shiny metal ass.
Ooh, yeah, come on, baby, yeah
Ooh, uh, come on, yeah...
Now that's hospital dancing.
Pretty good, eh, Calcy?
Good?
I've seen better acting from
extras in Godzilla movies.
I don't even remember shooting this scene.
We didn't.
That's security camera footage
from your dressing room.
He stole the scene and my money?
That's it!
I demand you fire this felonious ham!
The network execubots are coming!
Oh, dear God!
Presenting the president of the network.
Greetings, gentlemen.
You already know my execubots.
Executive Alpha, programmed
to like things it has seen before.
Hey, hey, hey.
Executive Beta, programmed to roll dice
to determine the fall schedule.
More reality shows.
And Executive Gamma,
programmed to underestimate
middle America.
It's funny, but is it going to
get them off their tractors?
Now, who put this obnoxious
dancing robot on my network?
We were about to fire him, sir.
Silence, hack!
We've been monitoring our
Nielsen families carefully,
and during the 12 seconds Bender
was onscreen,
viewer eyeball focus was up 90%.
But, sir, children watch this show.
Bender's no role model.
He's a filth monger.
At our network, we love filth.
Filthy rich, that is.
Being filthy rich, that is.
"Bite my shiny metal ass"
could be a catchphrase.
80% likely.
It will play in Peoria.
Game shows are back.
We need this edgy, sweeps-ready
robot on our network.
Bender, can you continue to drink, smoke
and steal things on TV?
Yes, I can.
We're gonna have a TV party tonight
All right
We're gonna have a TV party, all right!
All right!
We've got nothing better to do
Than watch TV and have a couple of brews
Gonna shoot things.
All our friends are gonna
hang out here tonight
All right!
We'll pass out on the couch, all right!
Yo, check out what I jacked from my dad.
A cigar?
Ripping.
Look, I'm Bender.
Ras H. Tafari, what's going on here?
The ruffians smoked one of your cigars.
That's not a cigar!
Uh, and it's not mine.
Hey, Dad, bite my shiny metal ass!
What? Such an act would be
most uncomfortable for both of us.
Where did you learn such language?
From Bender, my good jerkwad.
Bender, eh?
That guy's really
starting to twist my dreads.
Okay, okay, okay.
Get ready for this part.
Quiet, robot. Bender's on TV.
Oh, Calculon,
it's so good to get away from the city
and that beastly yet intriguing Bender.
Whoo!
And try this, kids at home.
Is television sensation Bender
a bad role model for Earth's children?
That's crazy.
A new protest group,
Father's Against Rude Television,
says, "Hell, yes."
What kind of bozos
would start a Bender protest group?
Good news, everyone.
Hermes and I have started
a Bender protest group.
That was uncanny.
Fathers Against Rude Television
don't want our kids watching
Bender's high-definition filth.
And for what?
Some kind of cheap laugh?
That's not what F.A.R.T. is all about.
No, sir. Not us FARTers.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! You can't censor me
just 'cause
I'm an obscenely bad role model.
As unclean as it makes me feel,
I agree with Bender.
Kids don't turn rotten
just from watching TV.
Yeah, give a little credit
to our public schools.
Our dads are all pumped up
on dorkosterone.
We're just trying to be cool, like Bender.
Yeah, and it's not even working.
Smoking and drinking make us barf.
Gentle jerkwads, I know how to
emulate Bender without barfing.
We could commit a burglary.
Hey, yeah!
Bender loves to burgle.
Hold up, though. Who could we rob?
We don't even know anyone with cool stuff.
Duh! We know someone who runs on
pure cool fuel... Bender.
- Whoa!
- We'll rob Bender.
TV gave us the idea.
You're watching Futurama,
the show that does not advocate
the cool crime of robbery.
Okay, it's crime time.
Hey, Bender.
Bust it
Okay, smarty, go to a party
Girls are scantily clad and showin' body
A chick walks by...
What's going on in here?
Oh, now I'm really outraged.
Where did you requisition this party?
And Zoidberg, what are you doing here?
I'm networking.
Let me give you my card.
Relax, Dad, we just invited
a few friends over.
Hmm...
There's something wrong with your story
but I can't put my finger on it.
Of course!
You don't have any friends!
Yeah, why do these popular kids
consider you cool all of a sudden?
Um, we're just cool is all.
Balderdash!
I'll be the judge of who's cool,
using the Coolometer.
Oh, yeah.
Good Lord, I'm getting a reading
of over 40 megafonzies.
Everybody out!
So, do you guys know about
anything else going on?
Because I'm totally still ready to party.
There's enough cool stuff here
to furnish a happening pad.
Where did it all come from?
Don't tell, comrades.
All for one and one for all!
We stole it!
Oh, crumb.
What? What's going on?
I'll tell you what.
Our boys have taken up stealing!
One of the worst and coolest of crimes.
And all from watching you on TV,
you cool jerk.
Hey, lay off me.
TV would stink if everyone on it
was a positive role model.
Bender is about entertainment, baby.
You can't hold me responsible
for what kids do when...
Hey, this is my stuff they stole!
That's the last straw!
Bender should not be
allowed on television!
Bender must be stopped.
I've gone too far.
Who does that guy think I am?
Come on, we're going to march
all the way to Hollywood
and make them stop forcing
their filthy me down our throats.
Down with Bender!
This mob's with me.
Go ahead.
Down with Bender! Down with Bender!
Down with Bender!
Down with...
...Bender!
Down with Bender!
As a doctor and captain
of this hospital ship,
I now pronounce you man and wife
with six months to live.
Listen up, Hollywood.
We're an exciting new mob.
You better believe it.
Great Shatner's ghost!
We demand that all TV
be equipped with a B-chip
that blocks Bender
from appearing on the screen.
Boo-yah!
I'm afraid the answer
is a gritty, in-your-face no.
Then I quit.
Then you don't quit.
I think you'll be finishing
the scene now, Mr. Bender,
and don't skimp on the nasty.
There'll be no further nasty.
We still have the option
of resorting to violence.
What makes you think that will work?
I saw it on TV in that episode
where Bender shot Calculon.
How cool was that.
Ooh, yeah, come on...
Quit the show.
Do the scene.
I'm a cold-blooded punk.
I once put a laugh track
on a sitcom that had no jokes in it.
Hey, look, the prop guy has a lamp.
Wha...
A-ha!
I was using that.
Listen up,
'cause I've got a climatic speech.
You, cameraman, keep the camera rolling.
You, director, give me my motivation.
You're angry.
Perfect.
Viewers of the world,
do smoking and drinking on TV
really make me cool?
Of course they do.
How about committing crimes and violence?
Again, the answer is yes.
But do we really want our kids exposed
to that kind of trash on TV?
I say absolutely not.
Ooh!
Uh, on the other hand, most,
perhaps all the blame
rests with the parents.
That's right, you.
And so I ask you this one question...
Have you ever tried simply
turning off the TV,
sitting down with your children
and hitting them?
We're just so busy.
Well, make time.
And, cut.
Good enough.
Splice in some reaction shots of me
and shove it on the air.
Have you ever tried
simply turning off the TV
sitting down with your children
and hitting them?
Well, I'd say we all
learned a valuable lesson
about TV there.
What was it?
Uh, that we should all take TV
a little less seriously.
And more importantly,
turn it off once in a while.
- Hear! Hear!
- Darn right.
So, should we turn it off now?
Well, uh, that depends what's on.
Nothing good.
Eh, let's just keep watching.
TV party tonight
Wha...
We've got nothing better to do
Than watch TV and have a couple of brews
Don't want to talk
about anything else
We don't want to know
We're dedicated, yes
To our favorite shows
All My Circuits
Everybody Loves Hypnotoad
Scary Door
Thursday Night Blernsball
Futurama